AoM Records 5593
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Series I. ADMINISTRATIVE RECORDS
  - Sub-Series E. Regional Division Records
    - Southwest Division, Annual Meeting, New Orleans, LA, 1980 (Box 81, Folder 19)
    - Southwest Division, Constitution and Bylaws, 1973-1979 (Box 81, Folder 20)
    - Southwest Division, Correspondence, 1979-1980 (Box 81, Folder 21)
    - Southwest Division, Regional Listing of Management Programs (Box 81, Folder 22)
    - Southwest Division, General, 1968-1980 (Box 81, Folder 23)
    - Southwest Division, General, 1973-1974 (Box 81, Folder 24-25)
    - Southwest Division, Proceedings, 1976-1983 (Box 82, Folder 1)
    - Southwestern Federation of Administrative Discp., Constitution, 1974 (Box 82, Folder 2)
    - Western Division, First, Second, Third Annual Meetings, Los Angeles, CA, Monterey, CA, Tempe, AZ, 1960-1962 (Box 83, Folder 1)
    - Western Division, Fourth, Fifth Annual Meetings, Seattle, WA, Monterey, CA, 1963-1964 (Box 83, Folder 2)
    - Western Division, Sixth Annual Meeting, San Diego, CA, 1965 (Box 83, Folder 3)
    - Western Division, Seventh Annual Meeting, Monterey, CA, 1966 (Box 83, Folder 4)
    - Western Division, Eighth Annual Meeting, Boulder, CO, 1967 (Box 83, Folder 5)
    - Western Division, Ninth Annual Meeting, Monterey, CA, 1968 (Box 83, Folder 6)
    - Western Division, Tenth Annual Meeting, Long Beach, CA, 1969 (Box 83, Folder 7)
    - Western Division, Eleventh Annual Meeting, Salt Lake City, UT, 1970 (Box 83, Folder 8)
    - Western Division, Twelfth Annual Meeting, Tucson, AZ, 1971 (Box 83, Folder 9)
    - Western Division, Thirteenth, Fourteenth Annual Meetings, Yosemite National Park, Reno, NV, 1972-1973 (Box 83, Folder 10)
    - Western Division, Fifteenth Annual Meeting, San Francisco, CA, 1974 (Box 83, Folder 11)
    - Western Division, Sixteenth Annual Meeting, Las Vegas, NV, 1975 (Box 83, Folder 12)
    - Western Division, 22nd Annual Meeting, California, 1981 (Box 83, Folder 13)
    - Western Division, Correspondence, 1958-1962 (Box 83, Folder 14)
    - Western Division, Correspondence, 1962-1964 (Box 83, Folder 15)
    - Western Division, Correspondence, 1964-1966 (Box 83, Folder 16)
    - Western Division, Correspondence, 1966-1967 (Box 83, Folder 17)
    - Western Division, Correspondence, 1967 (Box 83, Folder 18)
    - Western Division, Correspondence, 1967-1968 (Box 83, Folder 19)
    - Western Division, Correspondence, 1968 (Box 83, Folder 20)
    - Western Division, Correspondence, 1968-1974 (Box 83, Folder 21)
    - Western Division, Membership, 1967 (Box 83, Folder 22)
      Includes Academic Research and Backgrounds of Members
    - Western Division, Membership, 1967 (Box 83, Folder 23)
    - Western Division, Membership (Box 83, Folder 24)
    - Western Division, Membership (Box 83, Folder 25)
    - Western Division, General (Box 83, Folder 26)
    - Western Division, General, Applications, etc. (Box 83, Folder 27)
    - Western Division, Newsletter, 1977 (Box 83, Folder 28)
    - Western Academy Meeting, Jantzen Beach, OR, Correspondence, 1979 (Box 83, Folder 29)
      April 5-7, 1979
    - Regional Divisions, General Correspondence, 1962-1972 (Box 83, Folder 30)
    - European Division, Organization Correspondence, 1980 (Box 83, Folder 31)
  - Sub-Series F. Professional Division Records
    - Division of Business Policy and Planning, 1970-1971 (Box 84, Folder 1)
      Includes Correspondence Pertaining to the Establishment of This Division and Other Matters
    - Division of Business Policy and Planning, 1971 (Box 84, Folder 2)
      Includes memo (11/2/71) of Ackerman to members RE: Annual 1971 meeting, program planned for discussion, what are areas to be studies, what is policy
    - Division of Business Policy and Planning, 1972 (Box 84, Folder 3)
      Working Paper of Research Committee
    - Division of Business Policy and Planning, 1971 (Box 84, Folder 4)
      Report-Current Status and Plans for Division, November 1971
    - Division of Business Policy and Planning, 1971-1974 (Box 84, Folder 5)
    - Division of Business Policy and Planning, 1973 (Box 84, Folder 6)
      Paper on Research Strategy, February 1973
    - Division of Business Policy and Planning, 1974 (Box 84, Folder 7)
      Newsletter, Summer 1974
    - Division of Business Policy and Planning, 1976 (Box 84, Folder 8)
    - Division of Business Policy and Planning, 1979 (Box 84, Folder 9)
      Task Force Report on Research Workshop, August 1979
    - Division of Business Policy and Planning, 1976 (Box 84, Folder 10)
      "Research on Policy and Planning--The State of the Art," August 1976
    - Division of Business Policy and Planning, 1976 (Box 84, Folder 11)
      Research in Process, Report Response to Questionnaire, April 1976
    - Division of Business Policy and Planning, 1978 (Box 84, Folder 12)
      Correspondence from Chairman Chester W. Hofer, May 3, 1978
    - Division of Business Policy and Planning, 1978 (Box 84, Folder 13)
      Minutes, Business Meeting, February 1978
    - Division of Business Policy and Planning, 1978 (Box 84, Folder 14)
      Newsletter
    - Division of Business Policy and Planning (Box 84, Folder 15)
      Constitutions
    - Division of Business Policy and Planning (Box 84, Folder 16)
      Abstracts
    - Division of Business Policy and Planning (Box 84, Folder 17)
      Includes Final Schedule for National Meeting
    - Health Care, Administrative Division, Newsletter, 1976 (Box 84, Folder 18)
    - Health Care Division, 1980 (Box 84, Folder 19)
    - Human Resources Division, Correspondence, 1979-1980 (Box 84, Folder 20)
    - Division of International Management, 1969-1972 (Box 84, Folder 21)
      Correspondence: Wolf; Leon Meggison; Charles E. Summer, 1969-72
    - Division of International Management, 1972-1973 (Box 84, Folder 22)
    - Division of International Management, 1974 (Box 84, Folder 23)
    - Division of International Management, 1977-1978 (Box 84, Folder 24)
    - Division of International Management, 1979 (Box 84, Folder 25)
    - Division of International Management (Box 84, Folder 26)
    - Division of International Management, 1979 (Box 84, Folder 27)
    - Division of International Management (Box 84, Folder 28)
    - Management Education and Development Division (Box 85, Folder 1)
      includes Constitution of this Division; Newsletter; and Membership Directory
    - Management Education and Development Division, 1971-1977 (Box 85, Folder 2)
    - Management Education and Development Division, 1974 (Box 85, Folder 3)
    - Management Education and Development Division, 1974-1976 (Box 85, Folder 4)
      Includes Working Paper Series, Newsletter, Questionnaires, Data Analysis of a Survey on Prospects for Management Education, etc.
    - Management Education and Development Division, 1979 (Box 85, Folder 5)
      Membership Directory
    - Management Education and Development Division, Elections, 1979 (Box 85, Folder 6)
    - Management History Division, 1969-1971 (Box 85, Folder 7)
      Correspondence: Wolf, Robb, Hicks, Bedeian; Newsletter
    - Management History Division, 1971-1974 (Box 85, Folder 8)
    - Management History Division, 1980 (Box 85, Folder 9)
    - Management History Division, N-File Newsletter, 1973 (Box 85, Folder 10)
    - Management History Division, N-File Newsletter, 1980 (Box 85, Folder 11)
      Oct-80
    - Management History Division, N-File Newsletter, 1981 (Box 85, Folder 12)
      Feb-81
    - Management History Division, N-File Newsletter, 1981 (Box 85, Folder 13)
      Apr-81
    - Management History Division (Box 85, Folder 14)
    - Management History Division, 1971 (Box 85, Folder 15)
      Minutes of Organization Meeting, August 1971
    - Management History Division, 1973-1974 (Box 85, Folder 16)
      Minutes of 3rd Annual Meeting
    - Management History Division, 1973 (Box 85, Folder 17)
    - Management History Division, N-File, Newsletter, 1973-1974 (Box 85, Folder 18)
    - Management History Division, 1972 (Box 85, Folder 19)
      Minutes of 2nd Annual Meeting
    - Management History Division, Newsletter, 1983 (Box 85, Folder 20)
    - Management History Division, Charles Wrege Papers, 1975-1981 (Box 86, Folder ALL)
    - Management History Division, Charles Wrege Papers, 1983 (Box 87, Folder ALL)
    - Management History Division, Charles Wrege Papers, 1984 (Box 88, Folder 1-6)
    - Management History Division, Seidl, 1954-1968 (Box 88, Folder 7)
      History, Archives, Records Management, Requests for Information, Old Members
    - Management History Division, Julius C. Seidl, 1968 (Box 88, Folder 8)
      History, Archives
    - Management History Division, Julius C. Seidl, 1970-1971 (Box 88, Folder 9)
      History, Archives, Conversation with Seidl, Establishment of AM Archives at Florida University, Correspondence RE: Donations
    - Management History Division, Julius C. Seidl, 1971-1976 (Box 88, Folder 10)
      History, Archives, Report on First 10 Years of AM, 1971 Conversation with William Ryan (Archivist), Seidl-Historian
    - Management History Division, Past Presidents List, 1936-1956 (Box 88, Folder 11)
    - Managerial Consultation Division, Gore Correspondence, 1964-1985 (Box 89)
    - Managerial Consultation Division, 1979 (Box 90, Folder 1)
    - Managerial Consultation Division, Abstracts (Box 90, Folder 2)
    - Managerial Consultation Division, 1971 (Box 90, Folder 3)
      Correspondence: Wolf, Robert Wright
    - Managerial Consultation Division, 1972 (Box 90, Folder 4)
      Includes "Consultant's Communique" Vol. 1, No. 1, edited by Robert Wright
    - Managerial Consultation Division, 1973 (Box 90, Folder 5)
      Includes "Consultant's Communique" Vol. 1, No. 2, Vol. 3, No. 3, 1973
    - Managerial Consultation Division, 1977 (Box 90, Folder 6)
      "Consultant's Communique," March 1977
    - Manpower Division, 1969-1971 (Box 90, Folder 7)
      Correspondence: Max Wortman, Chairman
    - Manpower Division, 1974 (Box 90, Folder 8)
      Membership Listing
    - Manpower Division, 1972 (Box 90, Folder 9)
      Includes 1972 Program, and "New Patterns in Manpower Management Research" paper by James Walker, Indiana University; Newsletter
    - Organization Theory and Management Division, 1971-1975 (Box 90, Folder 10)
    - Division of Organizational Behavior, 1971-1972 (Box 90, Folder 11)
      Correspondence: Lyman Porter, Larry Cummings
    - Division of Organizational Behavior, 1971 (Box 90, Folder 12)
      Membership Listing, Minutes
    - Division of Organizational Behavior, 1973 (Box 90, Folder 13)
      Correspondence, Minutes
    - Division of Organizational Behavior, 1976 (Box 90, Folder 14)
      Minutes of Executive Committee Meeting
    - Division of Organizational Behavior (Box 90, Folder 15)
      Abstracts on Organizational Development
    - Division of Organizational Behavior (Box 90, Folder 16)
      Abstracts on Organization and Management Theory
    - Division of Organizational Behavior, 1979 (Box 90, Folder 17)
    - Division of Organizational Behavior (Box 90, Folder 18)
      Abstracts on Organizational Communication
    - Division of Organizational Behavior (Box 90, Folder 19)
    - Division of Organizational Behavior, 1974-1981 (Box 90, Folder 20)
      Membership Elections
    - Organizational Communications Division, 1973-1975 (Box 90, Folder 21)
      Correspondence: Hicks, Division's Newsletter
    - Organizational Development Division, 1971-1978 (Box 90, Folder 22)
      Correspondence: Wolf, Wendell French; Division's Newsletter
    - Organizational Management Theory, 1979 (Box 90, Folder 23)
    - Organizational Management Theory, 1978 (Box 90, Folder 24)
      Newsletter, September 1978
    - Organizational Theory (Box 90, Folder 25)
      Memo RE: Proposed Organizational Theory Doctoral Consortium
    - Personnel-Human Resources Division, Correspondence, 1974-1979 (Box 90, Folder 26)
    - Personnel and Organizational Management, 1976 (Box 90, Folder 27)
      Correspondence RE: Division Improvement
    - Production/Operations Management Division, 1969-1973 (Box 90, Folder 28)
      Correspondence: Jay R. Galbraith, Survey of Members' Interests- Objectives
    - Production/Operations Management Division, 1979 (Box 90, Folder 29)
    - Production/Operations Management Division, Correspondence, 1971-1972 (Box 90, Folder 30)
    - Production/Operations Management Division, 1974-1975 (Box 90, Folder 31)
      P/O "Perspectives," Premeeting ideas-George Gore, University of Cincinnati
    - Public Sector Division, 1975-1976 (Box 90, Folder 32)
    - Public Sector Division, Entrepreneurship Abstracts (Box 90, Folder 33)
    - Division of Research, 1971 (Box 91, Folder 1)
    - Social Issues in Management Division, 1971-1974 (Box 91, Folder 2)
    - Social Issues in Management Division, 1975-1984 (Box 91, Folder 3)
    - Ad Hoc Committee on Status of Women, 1974-1975 (Box 91, Folder 4)
    - Status of Women Interest Group Newsletter, 1979 (Box 91, Folder 5)
    - Status of Women Interest Group, 1981 (Box 91, Folder 6)
      Update Report
    - Status of Women Interest Group (Box 91, Folder 7)
      Materials RE: Boycott of ERA, Non-Ratification Status on Convention Centers
    - Professional Divisions, 1970-1971 (Box 91, Folder 8)
      Correspondence of Executive Board (Wolf) to Members Concerning the Establishment of the Divisions, Increase in Size, Special Interests
    - Professional Divisions-Policies (Box 91, Folder 9)
      Includes Information Regarding Development and Changes of Policies Concerning the Professional Divisions, Goals of the Divisions, etc.
    - Professional Divisions, Reports and Notes, 1972 (Box 91, Folder 10)
      Policy Manual Addenda on Professional Divisions, Resolutions of Professional Divisions
    - Professional Divisions, 1973 (Box 91, Folder 11)
      Correspondence: Hicks, Steven Carroll
    - Professional Divisions, 1973 (Box 91, Folder 12)
    - Professional Divisions, 1974 (Box 91, Folder 13)
      Report: Establishing Division of Health Care Administration
    - Professional Divisions, 1974 (Box 91, Folder 14)
    - Professional Divisions, 1975 (Box 91, Folder 15)
    - Professional Divisions, 1976 (Box 91, Folder 16)
      Includes Listing of Professional Divisions, Total Membership/Division and Overlap between Divisions
    - Professional Divisions (Box 91, Folder 17)
    - Professional Divisions (Box 91, Folder 18)
      Division Chairperson Information, undated
    - Professional Divisions, 1979-1980 (Box 91, Folder 19)
      Division Chairpersons
    - Professional Divisions, 1978 (Box 91, Folder 20)
      Territorial Domain Statement, William F. Glueck
  - Sub-Series G. Financial Records
    - Financial Records, Receipts and Disbursement, 1954 (Box 92, Folder 1)
    - Financial Records, 1949-1956 (Box 92, Folder 2)
      1/49 - 11/56
    - Financial Records, 1956-1957 (Box 92, Folder 3)
      11/56 - 12/57
    - Financial Records, 1957 (Box 92, Folder 4)
    - Financial Records, 1957 (Box 92, Folder 5)
    - Financial Records, Comparative Financial Statement, 1957-1958 (Box 92, Folder 6)
    - Financial Records, 1958 (Box 92, Folder 7)
      4/58 - 9/58
    - Financial Records, 1958-1959 (Box 92, Folder 8)
      11/58 - 12/59
    - Financial Records, 1958-1959 (Box 92, Folder 9)
      12/58 - 12/59
    - Financial Records, Comparative Financial Statement, 1959-1960 (Box 92, Folder 10)
    - Financial Records, 1960 (Box 92, Folder 11)
    - Financial Records, 1960 (Box 92, Folder 12)
    - Financial Records, 1961 (Box 92, Folder 13-17)
    - Financial Records, 1962 (Box 93, Folder 1-4)
    - Financial Records, 1963 (Box 93, Folder 5-7)
    - Financial Records, 1964 (Box 93, Folder 8)
    - Financial Records, 1965 (Box 93, Folder 9-13)
    - Financial Records, 1966 (Box 93, Folder 14)
    - Financial Records, Bank Statements, 1966 (Box 93, Folder 15)
      1/66 - 3/66
    - Financial Records, 1966-1967 (Box 93, Folder 16)
      4/66 - 10/67
    - Financial Records, Bank Statements, 1966 (Box 94, Folder 1)
      6/66 - 12/66
    - Financial Records, 1967 (Box 94, Folder 2)
      1/67 - 3/67
    - Financial Records, Bank Statements, 1967 (Box 94, Folder 3)
      4/67 - 6/67
    - Financial Records, Bank Statements, 1967 (Box 94, Folder 4)
      7/67 - 10/67
    - Financial Records, 1967 (Box 94, Folder 5)
    - Financial Records, 1967 (Box 94, Folder 6)
    - Financial Records, 1968 (Box 94, Folder 7)
    - Financial Records, 1968 (Box 94, Folder 8)
    - Financial Records, Bank Statements, 1969 (Box 94, Folder 9)
    - Financial Records, 1969 (Box 94, Folder 10)
    - Financial Records, 1970 (Box 94, Folder 11)
    - Financial Records, 1970 (Box 94, Folder 12)
    - Financial Records, Treasurer's Report, 1970 (Box 94, Folder 13)
    - Financial Records, Treasurer's Report, 1970 (Box 94, Folder 14)
    - Financial Records, Treasurer's Report, 1970 (Box 94, Folder 15)
    - Financial Records, 1971 (Box 94, Folder 16)
    - Financial Records, 1971 (Box 94, Folder 17)
    - Financial Records, Treasurer's Report, 1971 (Box 94, Folder 18)
    - Financial Records, 1972 (Box 94, Folder 19)
    - Financial Records, 1972 (Box 95, Folder 1-4)
    - Financial Records, Japanese Summer Escrow Account, 1972 (Box 95, Folder 5)
    - Financial Records, 1973 (Box 95, Folder 6)
    - Financial Records, 1972-1974 (Box 95, Folder 7)
    - Financial Records, 1974-1976 (Box 95, Folder 8)
    - Financial Records, 1975-1976 (Box 95, Folder 9)
    - Financial Records, Annual Report, 1976 (Box 95, Folder 10)
      Year Ended September 30, 1976
    - Financial Records, Academy of Management Annual Report, 1976 (Box 95, Folder 11)
      Year Ending, September 1976
    - Financial Records, Budget of the Academy, 1976-1977 (Box 95, Folder 12)
    - Financial Records, 1976-1977 (Box 95, Folder 13)
      Statement of Cash Receipts and Cash Disbursements, 10/1/76 - 9/30/77
    - Financial Records, 1972 (Box 95, Folder 14)
      Applications for Special Postal Rates
    - Financial Records, 1976-1977 (Box 95, Folder 15)
      Cash Receipts and Disbursements For Period 10/76 - 9/77
    - Financial Records, 1977-1978 (Box 95, Folder 16)
      Statement of Cash Receipts and Cash Disbursements, 10/1/77 - 3/31/78
    - Financial Records, 1977-1978 (Box 95, Folder 17)
      Proposed Budget
    - Financial Records, 1977-1978 (Box 95, Folder 18)
      Budget Materials
    - Financial Records, 1978 (Box 95, Folder 19)
      Annual Report for the Year Ended September 30, 1978
    - Financial Records, 1978 (Box 95, Folder 20)
      Annual Fiscal Report, Year Ended September 30, 1978
    - Financial Records, 1978 (Box 95, Folder 21)
      Annual Report, Year Ended September 1978
    - Financial Records, 1964-1971 (Box 95, Folder 22)
      Tax Status
    - Financial Records, 1975-1976 (Box 95, Folder 23)
      Budget of Academy, Includes Correspondence
    - Financial Records, 1978-1979 (Box 95, Folder 24)
      Receipts and Disbursement Statement, October 1, 1978 - March 31, 1979
    - Financial Records, 1979 (Box 95, Folder 25)
    - Financial Records, 1979-1980 (Box 95, Folder 26)
      Domestic vs. Foreign Postage
    - Financial Records, 1980 (Box 95, Folder 27)
      Annual CPA Audit
    - Financial Records (Box 96, Folder ALL)
  - Sub-Series H. Publications Award Files
    - Awards for Publications, Book Awards Program, Guidance for Book Evaluation (Box 97, Folder 1)
    - McKinsey Foundation Book Awards, 1961-1962 (Box 97, Folder 2)
      Statement of policy of awards under FNDN grant--Books which contribute to managers' and administrators' insights into managerial decision making, Correspondence: Smiddy (G.E.), Keith Davis; Warren Cannon (McKinsey Fdn)
    - Awards for Publications, McKinsey Foundation Book Awards Program, 1962 (Box 97, Folder 3)
    - McKinsey Foundation Book Awards, 1962-1963 (Box 97, Folder 4)
      Correspondence: Max Richards, Joseph Taggart (NYU), Smiddy, RE: 1963 Awards
    - Awards and Publications, McKinsey Book Awards, 1962-1963 (Box 97, Folder 5)
    - Publications Awards, McKinsey Foundation/Academy Book Awards, 1963-1964 (Box 97, Folder 6)
    - Awards and Publications, McKinsey Foundation Book Awards Program Report, 1963 (Box 97, Folder 7)
    - McKinsey Foundation Book Awards, 1963-1964 (Box 97, Folder 8)
      5 awards
    - Awards and Publications, McKinsey Book Awards, 1964 (Box 97, Folder 9)
    - McKinsey Foundation Book Awards, Statement of Policy, 1964 (Box 97, Folder 10)
    - McKinsey Foundation Book Awards, 1964 (Box 97, Folder 11)
    - McKinsey Foundation Book Awards, 1964-1965 (Box 97, Folder 12)
    - Awards for Publications, McKinsey Foundation Book Awards Program, Revised Program, 1965 (Box 97, Folder 13)
    - Awards for Publications, McKinsey Book Awards, 1965 (Box 97, Folder 14)
    - McKinsey Foundation Book Awards, 1965 (Box 97, Folder 15)
    - Awards for Publications, McKinsey Book Awards, 1966 (Box 97, Folder 16)
    - McKinsey Foundation Book Awards, 1966 (Box 97, Folder 17)
    - McKinsey Foundation Book Awards (Box 97, Folder 18)
      Correspondence: Smiddy, Cannon, Richard Viola (McKinsey Fdn)
    - McKinsey Foundation Book Awards, 1966 (Box 98, Folder 1)
    - McKinsey Foundation Book Awards, 1966 (Box 98, Folder 2)
    - McKinsey Foundation Book Awards, 1966 (Box 98, Folder 3)
    - Awards for Publications, McKinsey Book Awards, 1967 (Box 98, Folder 4)
    - Awards for Publications, McKinsey Book Awards, 1968 (Box 98, Folder 5)
    - Awards for Publications, McKinsey Book Awards, 1969 (Box 98, Folder 6)
    - Awards for Publications, McKinsey Book Awards, 1970 (Box 98, Folder 7)
    - Book Awards Council, 1966-1967 (Box 98, Folder 8)
      Correspondence Concerning the Academy's Decision to Break with the McKinsey Foundation
    - Book Awards Council, 1967-1968 (Box 98, Folder 9)
      Policy Statements, Finances, etc., Correspondence with Walter Hill (BAC, Chairman), Max Richards
    - Book Awards Council, 1969-1971 (Box 98, Folder 10)
      Correspondence: Paul Gordon (AM President, Wolf, Hill; Policy Statements--Judging Criteria, Nominations, How to Differentiate BAC from McKinsey
    - Awards Committee, Correspondence, 1960-1965 (Box 98, Folder 11)
    - Awards Committee, Correspondence, 1966 (Box 98, Folder 12)
  - Sub-Series G. Miscellaneous
    - Council for International Progress in Management (CIPM), 1966-1968 (Box 99, Folder 1)
    - Council for International Progress in Management (CIPM), 1968-1972 (Box 99, Folder 2)
      Correspondence: Steiner, CIPM as Liaison Organization Provides AM information on various international problems, i.e. control of MNCS
    - Council for International Progress in Management (CIPM), 1962-1963 (Box 99, Folder 3)
      Brochures, Correspondence RE: Organizational Problems in CIPM; Elliott Haynes (CIPM President)
    - Council for International Progress in Management (CIPM), 1963-1966 (Box 99, Folder 4)
      Access to CIPM-International Management Organization, AM member of CDPM
    - Council for Professional Education for Business (CPEB), 1967-1970 (Box 99, Folder 5)
    - Council for Professional Education for Business (CPEB), 1970-1972 (Box 99, Folder 6)
    - Council for Professional Education for Business (CPEB), 1967 (Box 99, Folder 7)
    - Council for Professional Education for Business (CPEB), 1955-1966 (Box 99, Folder 8)
      Correspondence with American Assoc. of College School of Business
    - Computer Printout of Some Questionnaire Responses on SPSS (Box 99, Folder 9)
    - Distinguished Scholar Award, Academy of Management (Box 99, Folder 10)
    - Fellows of the Academy, Honorary Position-Fellows Noted on Themselves, Lists-Documentation of Selection Process, 1956-1961 (Box 99, Folder 11)
    - Fellows of the Academy, 1968-1969 (Box 99, Folder 12)
    - Fellows of the Academy, 1969-1972 (Box 99, Folder 13)